<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>CyFun</title><link>https://s4ch.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on CyFun</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:30:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s4ch.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>eBPF JIT Compiler Internals: Understanding Constant Blinding Implementation</title><link>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/ebpf-jit-compiler-internals-understanding-constant-blinding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/ebpf-jit-compiler-internals-understanding-constant-blinding/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://s4ch.github.io/EBPF_logo.png" alt="eBPF Logo" />
&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Disclaimer&lt;/strong>: This research is conducted independently during my personal time as an open-source security researcher. The views and findings presented here are my own and do not represent or reflect the opinions of my current employer or any affiliated organizations.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="introduction">Introduction&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>eBPF has become ubiquitous in modern Linux systems, powering everything from network filtering to system observability tools.While the eBPF verifier gets most of the security attention, the Just-In-Time (JIT) compiler that translates eBPF bytecode to native machine instructions contains equally fascinating security mechanisms that deserve deeper analysis.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Attackers Are Weaponizing OAuth to Silently Take Over Microsoft Outlook Accounts</title><link>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/oath-exploited-by-attackers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/oath-exploited-by-attackers/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="tldr">TL;DR&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Last week, while investigating some suspicious Microsoft Outlook activity for a client at iZOOlogic, I stumbled upon something that made my heart sink for a while. What started as a routine incident response engagement turned into the discovery of one of the most sophisticated OAuth phishing campaigns I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in my experience so far of security research.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here&amp;rsquo;s the kicker - this attack doesn&amp;rsquo;t steal your password. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about your MFA. Instead, it tricks you into granting a malicious application complete access to your mailbox, and it does it so smoothly that most users won&amp;rsquo;t think twice before clicking &amp;ldquo;Accept.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Novel approach to tackle UAF Bugs in the Linux Kernel</title><link>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/bucket-allocators/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 06:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/bucket-allocators/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi, kernel and sec enthusiasts! It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since my last post(2022), but I&amp;rsquo;ve got something juicy for you today. We are going to dive into an exciting new proposal that aims to bolster the Linux kernel&amp;rsquo;s defenses against those persistent use-after-free (UAF) vulnerabilities. Grab your favorite beverage or drink(Try Amul Kool once, Thank me later), because we&amp;rsquo;re about to get our hands dirty with some kernel internals!&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-persistent-threat-of-uaf-vulnerabilities">The Persistent Threat of UAF Vulnerabilities&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>If you&amp;rsquo;ve been in the low-level security for a while, you&amp;rsquo;re probably sick of hearing about UAF vulnerabilities. But for those who need a refresher, UAFs occur when a program continues to use a pointer to memory after it&amp;rsquo;s been freed. This can lead to all sorts of fun exploitation scenarios, especially in kernel-land where the stakes are highest.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/ebpf_jit_compiler_internals_understanding_constant_blinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://s4ch.github.io/blog/ebpf_jit_compiler_internals_understanding_constant_blinding/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://s4ch.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://s4ch.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hey-there-im-sachin-">Hey there, I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;a href="https://linkedin.com/in/sachinkumardhaka">Sachin&lt;/a> 👋&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Security Engineer from India working with a US cybersecurity firm, doing purple team work. Got my BTech from MNIT Jaipur in 2024.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I focus on &lt;strong>eBPF security&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>EDR research&lt;/strong>, and &lt;strong>threat intelligence&lt;/strong>. My work ranges from analyzing eBPF internals to hunting down C2 infrastructure and tracking phishing campaigns.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="what-im-into">What I&amp;rsquo;m Into&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>eBPF Security&lt;/strong>: JIT compilers, verifier bypasses, and detection/evasion techniques&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>EDR Research&lt;/strong>: Understanding detection engines and bypass methods&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://s4ch.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://s4ch.github.io/contact/</guid><description>How to get in touch</description></item></channel></rss>